#The Simpsons #
D'oh!
I can't believe it!
We won another contest.
- The Simpsons are going to Delaware!
- I wanna see Wilmington!
- I wanna visit a screen door factory.
- Yep.
Delaware's got it all.
You're next, Mr. Simpson.
- Hey, wait a minute. Airport tax: Five dollars?
- Sir, it's a standard fee.
Well, we are not boarding that plane
unless you waive that tax.
Waive it!
Stupid anti-fist-shaking laws!
The Simpsons are riding the rails!
Cool. A dead hobo.
Mornin', folks.
- What are you gonna do to us?
- Now, don't worry.
I'm not a stabbin' hobo.
I'm a singin' hobo.
# Nothin' beats the hobo life #
# Stabbin' folks with my hobo knife #
- # I gouge them-##
- Excuse me, Hobo.
Can you play something
a little less unnerving?
Sure.
I was just having a little fun
with you "nobos."
Uh, here's a ballad that'll
set fire to your trash can.
#Won't you listen to my tale
that's 10 stories tall #
# 'Bout a king-sized woodsman
name a Bunyan, comma, Paul #
Congratulations, Mr. Bunyan.
It's a boy!
Jeezum crow!
- How was it, honey?
- Whiskey, please.
Me "hungee."
# Born mighty big
he continued to expand #
# Thanks to a hopped-up
pituitary gland #
Hey!
I'll get ya!
# His body grew big
but his brain stayed small #
# He was tree-choppin', friend-stompin'
house-crushin'Paul ##
Me hungee!
Time to make Paul's breakfast.
Hey, Paul, flapjacks!
Flapjacks!
Out of the frying pan!
Yuck! All right, uh,
let's get started on lunch.
- And-Wait. Where's Lenny?
- Hello?
Can anybody hear me?
I think I found a way out.
It's not pretty, but it'll do.
All right, look, we gotta
do something about Bunyan.
We're going bankrupt
just feedin' and clothin' the guy...
not to mention the crushings.
Hey, I say we get him drunk
and drag him out of town.
Same way we got rid of
Laura Ingalls Wilder.
Yeah, that's a great idea!
Hmm.
Uh, hey, Paulie?
What say we buy you a beer?
Aw, you guys are the greatest friends
a giant doofus could have.
Good Lord!
Brought down by one beer?
And a couple of these babies.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm off to the barn dance.
Watch his head.
Where am I?
Oh, they don't want me anymore.
# Paul was just as lonely
as a man could get #
# So he took out his ax
and he carved himself a pet ##
And now-
Oh, boy.
I wish you were real.
Mmm.
Hey, what the-
Oh, it's a miracle!
I'll call you Babe.
You'll be my best friend.
So Paul and his blue ox Babe...
traveled all across this great land,
leavin'their mark.
Excuse me. Paul Bunyan
never fought Rodan.
And his size seems to be
really inconsistent.
I mean, one minute,
he's 10 feet tall.
The next,
his feet are as big as a lake.
- Hey, hey, hey! Who's the hobo here?
- I'm just sayin'.
# Now Paul and Babe
were a mighty fine match #
- # But the man had an itch
that an ox couldn't scratch ##
- Huh?
She's pretty.
Oh. What a handsome man.
Got ya!
Don't worry.
I won't smush you.
- You're cute.
- Oh. Thank you.
Hey, what are you doing?
- I just wanna spruce up for our date.
- Oh.
Whoo-hoo!
Mmm!
Oh!
We've been together a long time now.
- When are we gonna, you know-
- Soon.
I just need a few more yoga classes.
Oh, look!
A shooting star.
Hey, that meteor's
headed straight for us...
with the fire and the impact
and the 100% chance of pain!
Pain in the glayvin!
God has sent this fiery kill rock
to show us his love.
No! We're gonna die!
There's only one man
who can save us.
Oh, I get it.
When I'm crushing and killing you,
you don't like me.
But when I can save your life,
suddenly I'm Mr. Popular.
Yeah. That's pretty much it.
Whoo-hoo!
I'm Mr. Popular!
Come on.
Right across the plate.
Let's see what you got, huh?
This one's for the little crippled boy...
that I crippled.
You can do it, Paul!
Gimme a kiss for luck.
Ow! Hot!
Oh, boy, that's-
Oh, come on!
Ow!
And that's how Paul Bunyan
started the great Chicago fire.
Boy, that story had everything.
- A giant, house crushing, a meteor-
- Townspeople.
Got any more tall tales?
Well, I suppose I could
spin ya a few more yarns.
But first, who wants to give
me a sponge bath? I'm filthy.
All right.
But your next story...
better be worth it.
Get in there good.
Yeah, that's it.
Don't be shy.
There you go.
Okay. Ready for another impression?
This is SouthsideJake
tearing into Tin Can Tilly.
Oh, this'll be good!
"Who put the beans in my bindle?"
"I am so tired of you saying
that I put beans in your bindle!
It just makes me so"-
"Do you ever shut up?"
"Kiss me, you fool!"
Uh, could we hear another tall tale?
In a sec.
All righty.
Here's a story just for you, little girl.
It's the tale ofJohnny-
No. Connie Appleseed.
Oh.
Back around 1840...
the great pie known as America...
was still cooling
on the windowsill...
and everybody headed west
for a slice.
# Cleaning my gun with the safety off
safety off, safety off #
# Cleaning my gun with the-##
Whoopsie.
Dad, you just killed
a poor defenseless buffalo.
A poor, delicious buffalo.
He'll be dinner for the whole wagon train.
- Why'd you kill another one?
- Dessert.
Ow!
Hey, I found a bullet.
- Man, buffalo are easy to kill.
- People...
if you don't stop this slaughter,
you'll wipe out the buffalo.
Wipe out an entire species?
Why, that's impossible.
Why is it we have ladders
that can put a man on the roof...
but we can't find a
renewable source of food?
Think, Connie. Think.
- Connie.
- Wha-
Connie.
That tree! It seems to be calling to me.
Of course! Apples!
No, Connie, over here!
Help me!
Mom, Dad, look what I found!
Oh, boy!
Buffalo testicles!
- Mmm!
- No, Dad, they're apples.
Yuck!
Well, that's it. I don't want anything
to do with this wagon train of death.
Either switch to apples,
or go on without me.
Hmm!
You'll be sorry!
Oh!
So Connie roamed the prairie alone...
planting apples seeds
all along the way.
She even changed
her last name to Appleseed.
And her family
changed theirs to Bufflekill.
I haven't had buffalo in six hours.
Marge...
how about whipping up
some buffalo sausage...
huevos buffaleros,
and some fresh-squeezed buffal-O. J?
The buffalo are gone.
I think you shot them all.
Oh! Connie was right!
We wiped out the entire species!
What have I done?
Calm down, Pa.
There's two left.
What have I done?
With the buffalo gone, the starving
settlers were driven to cannibalism.
You're the fattest, Bufflekill.
Okay, everybody, dig in!
Stop! I've got apples!
Delicious, nutritious apples.
And there's enough for everyone.
Sweet!
It's like a hootenanny in my mouth!
- We're saved!
- It's a miracle!
- Hooray for Connie Bufflekill!
- What?
So now we're not eating Homer?
And thanks to that little girl...
today you can find apples
in everything that's good.
Apple wine, apple whiskey...
apple schnapps, apple martinis...
uh, Snapple with vodka in it...
apple nail polish remover-
Don't forget applesauce.
Yeah. I suppose you could
grind some pills into it.
Aw.
- Look out there, folks. That's the mighty Mississip.
- Big deal.
Reminds me of a tall tale
about two scalawags...
rafting down the Big Muddy-
Tom Sawyer and Huck Finn.
That's not a tall tale.
It's a book by Mark Twain.
Look, let's just do this thing.
Whitewashing sucks, Tom.
It powerful sucks.
Morning, friend.
Want your turn at whitewashin'?
It's powerful fun.
Why, you ain't fooling me again,
Tom Sawyer.
If I may.
Now get to work!
I still got it.
Now, Huckleberry Finn,
you get down from there.
A body could break his neck.
I ain't afeard of that.
I'd just get a new neck off n a cat.
Huck!
Oh, Huck, you gave your bones
an awful rattling.
Yeah. But I'm feeling
better right now.
- Aha!
- Papa!
Hold my daughter's hand, will ya?
I was gonna let go by-and-by.
Well, I guess there's no harm done
as long as it was gonna be by-and-by.
But just to play it safe-
We're gathered here today to force this man...
Huckleberry Finn,
into holy matrimony.
How romantic.
This reminds me
of our shotgun wedding.
Grandpa, we've been
married for years.
When are you gonna
put down that gun?
Well, I reckon you're right.
Hang it all!
Do you, Huck,
take Becky as your wife?
Whoa!
Hey, they done switched
the groom with a pig!
- No wonder he was pooping so much.
- Ha-ha!
Come on!
Let's get those polecats!
Oh! Now we'll never catch 'em!
I reckon we're safe now.
There's the state line.
Uh-oh!
Rapids!
Please do not exit the raft...
until it has come
to a complete stop.
Mr. Silas, this young lady's
flashing her privates.
Oh! Well, I'll dispose of this!
All for Silas. All for Silas.
I'm considerable hungry.
We got any food left?
Hmm. Looks like
we're out of corn pone...
fatback, hardtack,
fat pone, "corntack."
- Any "tackback"?
- "Tackback"?
- I mean "backtack."
- Plumb out.
One jug of whiskey,
three plugs of"tobacky"...
and some extra-strength opium.
- That will be two cents, boys.
- Two cents?
Hey, if you think my prices are high,
go across the street.
Thank you. Come again.
- He put the lard pone on top of the egg pone.
- Dang!
Double dang!
Aw, donkey butter!
Oh, it's no use.
I got an idea.
Uh- Hmm.
Well, dog my cats.
They's dis-apporated.
Keep quiet, Huck. They won't look up here
if nothing draws their attention.
# Old man river #
# That old man river#
# He just keeps rolling #
Well, I see President Fillmore
is in the news again.
Glug, glug, glug.
What'll it be, boys?
- Just three X's for me.
- Give me five.
This ain't no five-X whiskey.
I can still see.
That barkeep's a no-good cheat!
Cheat?
Eh-All right.
We've all got derringers.
Now let's just put 'em away.
Nobody here is a cheat.
- Cheat?
- Aw, geez.
Man, those derringer bullets
are weak.
Powerful weak.
Light out, and stay lit out!
Aw, catfish.
Let us pray for the souls of these
dearly departed young men...
Huckleberry Finn and Thomas Sawyer.
Now for the traditional lowering
of the bodies into the coffins.
And that was Tom and Huck's
last adventure.
I liked that story,
'cause I was a judge.
Delaware!
Well, this is our stop. Would you
like to come sightseeing with us?
We're gonna visit the place where
JCPenney sends their damaged merchandise.
No, thanks.
I'm gonna keep on ridin' the rails...
swappin' stories for sponge baths.
I believe I told three stories.
Oh!
I'll meet you in Wilmington.
Close the door.
Raise your arm. Okay, the other one.
You know, I do, uh, 400 sit-ups a day.
Oh, it shows.
I was gonna say something...
- but I thought it might sound, you know, weird.
- Oh, not at all.
I like when people
say nice things about my body.
And it's important
to feel good about yourself.
Okay, spread your toes.
Oh!
You know how much glass is in here?
Shh!
Oh, boy! Buffalo testicles!
www.tvsubtitles.net